{
	"id": 5,
	"title": "Lesson 5",
	"description": "Everyday objects and how to say what you have",
	"content": [
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Mo ena ene", "ek trwa sez."],
			"answer": "latab",
			"options": ["latab", "manz", "liv"],
			"translation": "I have a table and three chairs."
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Li", "ene portab lor latab."],
			"answer": "ena",
			"options": ["manz", "ena", "liv"],
			"translation": "He has a phone on the table."
		},
		{
			"type": "fillBlank",
			"question": ["Zot", "liv dan lakaz."],
			"answer": "ena",
			"options": ["liv", "ena", "sez"],
			"translation": "They have books in the house."
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"house": "lakaz",
				"table": "latab",
				"chair": "sez",
				"phone": "portab"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "match",
			"options": {
				"book": "liv",
				"clothes": "linz",
				"watch": "mont",
				"glasses": "linet"
			}
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'table'?",
			"answer": "latab",
			"options": ["sez", "latab", "lakaz"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'glasses'?",
			"answer": "linet",
			"options": ["liv", "linet", "linz"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'chair'?",
			"answer": "sez",
			"options": ["tab", "sez", "mont"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'I have'?",
			"answer": "Mo ena",
			"options": ["Mo ena", "Mo garson", "Mo linet"]
		},
		{
			"type": "multipleChoice",
			"question": "How do you say 'book'?",
			"answer": "liv",
			"options": ["liv", "dipain", "linz"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "I have a phone",
			"answer": "Mo ena ene portab",
			"options": ["Mo", "ene", "ena", "portab", "liv"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "He has a chair",
			"answer": "Li ena ene sez",
			"options": ["Li", "sez", "ena", "ene", "latab"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "Mo ena ene liv",
			"answer": "I have a book",
			"options": ["book", "a", "I", "have", "phone"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "Zot ena ene lakaz",
			"answer": "They have a house",
			"options": ["They", "house", "have", "a", "book"]
		},
		{
			"type": "translate",
			"question": "He has a watch",
			"answer": "Li ena ene mont",
			"options": ["mont", "Li", "ene", "ena", "linet"]
		}
	],
	"vocabulary": {
		"house": "lakaz",
		"table": "latab",
		"chair": "sez",
		"phone": "portab",
		"book": "liv",
		"clothes": "linz",
		"watch": "mont",
		"glasses": "linet",
		"have": "ena"
	}
}
